# **ANDY ANDERSON**

En thus iastic car sales man with nine years of experience closing deals on vanous makes a nild First Avenue, models. Able to understand and breakdown vehicle features and dealership offers for cu stom e rs. H igh -l evel l i ste n i ng ski 11 s a l low for a comp lete u ndersta nd ing of cu stom e rs' needs, facilitating sales. A persuasive but respectful negotiator who works to leave both parties satisfied.

Tacoma, WA11111 a. a n d erson@emai I .com (111)111-1111

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### SENIOR SALES ASSOCIATE

Tacoma Toyota, Tacoma, WA November 2016- Present

- Build relationships with new and repeat customers, helping expand the dealership's customer base by 4% and total annual sales by 3% to date
- Explain financing options to buyersand coordinate deals with the dealership's financing team
- Understand vehicles' features and communicate them to buyers in clear language
- Accompany buyers on an average of 24 test drives per month
- Persuasively suggest warranties, maintaining an upsell rate 5% higher than the dealership's average

#### JUNIOR SALES ASSOCIATE

Seattle Ford, Seattle, WA July 2012-October 2016

- Greeted walk-in customers at the doorand directed them to the proper department
- Handled approximately 15 trade-in negotiations per month
- Explained maintenance packages on new and used vehicles
- Took phone calls and responded to emails from prospective buyers about online listings
- Followed up with customers after purchases to ensure satisfaction

#### **EDUCATION**

High School Diploma Tacoma High School, Tacoma, WA September 2008 - June 2012

## **KEY SKILLS**

- Customer service
- Mic rosoft Wo rd, Excel, a n d O utloo k software
- Explaining vehicles'perks
- Researching competitors'prices

### **CERTIFICATIONS**

Sales Management Certification, National Automobile Dealers Association, 2018